# Mahima Bhutani

## **UX DESIGNER**

Since my early days, I had utmost fascination for different human perception and decision-making process. It was only later that I realised, I want to influence and gratify these humanly experiences. Since then, I have devoted myself to User Experience Research and Design.

I have delivered multiple projects both as a member of a skilled team as well as independently. The projects were in different fields and settings providing an all-round development. I have learnt to be persistent and solve problems in creative ways, while still playing well with others.

## **SKILLS**

#### Design

Sketch, Figma, InVision, XD, Photoshop; Mobile & Web UI; Wireframing & Mockups

#### **User Research**

Data & Task Analysis; Persona Building; A/B Testing; User Interviews; Usability Testing

#### **Front-End Development**

JavaScript; ReactJS; HTML; CSS; Bootstrap

#### **Soft Skills**

Market Research; Presentation Skills; Financial Evaluation; Team Management;

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2019

M.Sc. Human Computer Interaction and Design

KTH Royal Instituite of Technology, Sweden

2011 - 2015

**B.Tech. Computer Science** 

Jaypee University of engineering and Technology, India

Portfolio

www.bhutani.design

Mail

mahima@bhutani.design

Call

+46 72 842 6311

LinkedIn Profile

linkedin.com/in/mahimabhutani

# **EXPERIENCE**

2017 - Present

#### **UX/UI** Designer

#### Freelancer

Designed various mobile apps and web applications for multiple companies as a freelancer

Jan 2019 - June 2019

### UX Designer as Master Thesis Worker

#### Scania CV

Responsible for designing and developing portal using information visualization technique for internal workers of the organisation for better decision making.

Nov 2015 - June 2017

## Solution Integrator

#### Ericsson

Responsible for maintenance of Order Management system for Telecom operators which enables management of customer data like billing, revenue, personal information etc.

2014 Summer

#### Intern

#### Kleward consulting Pvt. Ltd.

Creation of an interactive web response system for the admin panel. Was responsible for coding, testing and maintenance of the live system. Released a system currently used by World Famous-Tech Observer Admin.